<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on  Paul Efren...</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on  Paul Efren...</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogdown Tutorial.</title>
      <link>/note/2018/09/07/another-note/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/note/2018/09/07/another-note/</guid>
      <description>Este sitio fue construido siguiendo los tutoriales escritos por:
 Allison Hill Up and running with blogdown .   Amber Thomas Making a Website Using Blogdown, Hugo, and GitHub pages.   Emi Tanaka Blinging up your website built with hugo via blogdown R package.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intervalos de Confianza</title>
      <link>/post/2018/09/07/intervalos-de-confianza/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2018/09/07/intervalos-de-confianza/</guid>
      <description>This is a modification of a blog written by Sean Kross, using tidyverse.
Esta es una modificación de un blog escrito por Sean Kross1, utilizando tidyverse2.
=======This is a modification of a blog written by Sean Kross1, using tidyverse2.
Esta es una modificación de un blog escrito por Sean Kross3, utilizando tidyverse4.
 0cd206485c3598bde20cb020bcbea6544a4204aaImagina que estás buscando estimar el promedio de una alguna característica de una población.Conformada por 100 000 individuos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Paul Efren</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi! I&amp;rsquo;m Paul, a plant ecologist, and data enthusiast. I am a biologist from the Universidad Nacional de San Antonio Abad del Cusco - Peru.
I have worked in tropical forest ecology since 2013. I have gained experience in conservation projects with Frankfurt Zoological Society Peru. I also have collaborated extensively with the Andes Biodiversity and Ecosystem Research Group for around 5 years. ABERG working in the Andes and Amazon regions of Peru such as Manu National Park-Peru and surroundings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curriculum Vitae</title>
      <link>/content/vitae/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/content/vitae/</guid>
      <description>Paul Efren Santos AndradeContac Information:Email paulefrens@gmail.com
Twitter PaulEfrenSantos
InterestsOpen Science.Data Managing.Data visualization.Plant Ecology.Functional Traits.EDUCATION:2014 Bachelor on Biological Science. Universidad Nacional San Antonio Abad del Cusco.
2016 Biologist. Universidad Nacional San Antonio Abad del Cusco.
POST GRADUATE COURSES:2013 Why and how to measure functional characters of plants? - A practical introduction, University of Oxford and Núcleo Diversus.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>